{
  "name": "Reizināšana ar 2",
  "level": 1,
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 13,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 2 × 1?",
      "correctAnswer": 2,
      "options": [1, 2, 3, 4]
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 2 × 2?",
      "correctAnswer": 4,
      "options": [2, 3, 4, 5]
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 2 × 3?",
      "correctAnswer": 6,
      "options": [5, 6, 7, 8]
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 2 × 4?",
      "correctAnswer": 8,
      "options": [6, 7, 8, 9]
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 2 × 5?",
      "correctAnswer": 10,
      "options": [8, 9, 10, 11]
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 2 × 6?",
      "correctAnswer": 12,
      "options": [10, 11, 12, 13]
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 2 × 7?",
      "correctAnswer": 14,
      "options": [12, 13, 14, 15]
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 2 × 8?",
      "correctAnswer": 16,
      "options": [14, 15, 16, 17]
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 2 × 9?",
      "correctAnswer": 18,
      "options": [16, 17, 18, 19]
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 2 × 10?",
      "correctAnswer": 20,
      "options": [18, 19, 20, 21]
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 2 × 11?",
      "correctAnswer": 22,
      "options": [20, 21, 22, 23]
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "prompt": "What is 2 × 12?",
      "correctAnswer": 24,
      "options": [22, 23, 24, 25]
    }
  ]
}
